<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>High Risk Payment Gateway Archives - PayGate.to</title>
	<atom:link href="https://paygate.to/high-risk-payment/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/high-risk-payment/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 08:54:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/cropped-New-Project-10-32x32.png</url>
	<title>High Risk Payment Gateway Archives - PayGate.to</title>
	<link>/high-risk-payment/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>White-label API Custom Domain Guide</title>
		<link>/white-label-api-custom-domain-guide/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[paygate.to]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 20:43:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[High Risk Payment Gateway]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1559</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this tutorial you will learn how to use your own custom domain with our payment gateway API. You will be able to use your own domain instead of api.paygate.to and checkout.paygate.to. You will also be able to optionally insert your affiliate wallet to earn 0.5% on every sale your sub-merchant receive. You need to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://paygate.to/white-label-api-custom-domain-guide/">White-label API Custom Domain Guide</a> appeared first on <a href="https://paygate.to/">PayGate.to</a>.</p>
]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fixing Common Issues with WHMCS Payment Module</title>
		<link>/whmcs-payment-gateway-troubleshooting/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[paygate.to]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:25:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[High Risk Payment Gateway]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1517</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this page we will go through troubleshooting most common issues regarding WHMCS payment gateway module. Our WHMCS payment gateway module is fully tested and it should be automatically processing all paid invoices by default once you set it up. However due to other badly coded modules installed on your website or other wrong settings [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://paygate.to/whmcs-payment-gateway-troubleshooting/">Fixing Common Issues with WHMCS Payment Module</a> appeared first on <a href="https://paygate.to/">PayGate.to</a>.</p>
]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fixing Common Issues with WooCommerce Payment Gateway Plugin</title>
		<link>/woocommerce-payment-gateway-troubleshooting/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[paygate.to]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 21:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[High Risk Payment Gateway]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1488</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this page we will go through troubleshooting most common issues regarding WooCommerce payment gateway plugin. Our WooCommerce payment gateway plugin is fully tested and it should be automatically processing all paid orders by default once you set it up. However due to other badly coded plugins installed on your website or other wrong settings [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://paygate.to/woocommerce-payment-gateway-troubleshooting/">Fixing Common Issues with WooCommerce Payment Gateway Plugin</a> appeared first on <a href="https://paygate.to/">PayGate.to</a>.</p>
]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>WooCommerce High Risk Payment Gateway</title>
		<link>/woocommerce-high-risk-payment-gateway/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[paygate.to]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 17:47:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[High Risk Payment Gateway]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=495</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Unlocking Payment Potential for High-Risk Merchants: Introducing the Rest API Plugin from PayGate.to In the world of e-commerce, the thrill of selling high-risk products can often be dampened by the struggles of finding suitable payment processors. If you&#8217;re tired of facing rejections and bans from payment providers like Stripe and PayPal due to the nature [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://paygate.to/woocommerce-high-risk-payment-gateway/">WooCommerce High Risk Payment Gateway</a> appeared first on <a href="https://paygate.to/">PayGate.to</a>.</p>
]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hide What You are Selling From Skrill and Bypass Suspended High Risk Account</title>
		<link>/hide-what-you-are-selling-from-skrill-and-bypass-suspended-high-risk-account/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[paygate.to]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 17:40:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[High Risk Payment Gateway]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hide-what-you-are-selling-from-skrill-and-bypass-suspended-high-risk-account/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are you tired of getting banned or restricted by Skrill? This is your perfect solution!!! If you are running a high risk business like dropshipping, SMM, SARM or any other form of high risk business you may face a big problem finding a high risk payment processor to accept your business model. Our WooCommerce plugin [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://paygate.to/hide-what-you-are-selling-from-skrill-and-bypass-suspended-high-risk-account/">Hide What You are Selling From Skrill and Bypass Suspended High Risk Account</a> appeared first on <a href="https://paygate.to/">PayGate.to</a>.</p>
]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hide What You are Selling From Shopify Payments and Bypass Suspended High Risk Account</title>
		<link>/hide-what-you-are-selling-from-shopify-payments-and-bypass-suspended-high-risk-account/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[paygate.to]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 17:40:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[High Risk Payment Gateway]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hide-what-you-are-selling-from-shopify-payments-and-bypass-suspended-high-risk-account/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are you tired of getting banned or restricted by Shopify Payments? This is your perfect solution!!! If you are running a high risk business like dropshipping, SMM, SARM or any other form of high risk business you may face a big problem finding a high risk payment processor to accept your business model. Our WooCommerce [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://paygate.to/hide-what-you-are-selling-from-shopify-payments-and-bypass-suspended-high-risk-account/">Hide What You are Selling From Shopify Payments and Bypass Suspended High Risk Account</a> appeared first on <a href="https://paygate.to/">PayGate.to</a>.</p>
]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hide What You are Selling From Payline Data and Bypass Suspended High Risk Account</title>
		<link>/hide-what-you-are-selling-from-payline-data-and-bypass-suspended-high-risk-account/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[paygate.to]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 17:40:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[High Risk Payment Gateway]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hide-what-you-are-selling-from-payline-data-and-bypass-suspended-high-risk-account/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are you tired of getting banned or restricted by Payline Data? This is your perfect solution!!! If you are running a high risk business like dropshipping, SMM, SARM or any other form of high risk business you may face a big problem finding a high risk payment processor to accept your business model. Our WooCommerce [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://paygate.to/hide-what-you-are-selling-from-payline-data-and-bypass-suspended-high-risk-account/">Hide What You are Selling From Payline Data and Bypass Suspended High Risk Account</a> appeared first on <a href="https://paygate.to/">PayGate.to</a>.</p>
]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hide What You are Selling From NMI and Bypass Suspended High Risk Account</title>
		<link>/hide-what-you-are-selling-from-nmi-and-bypass-suspended-high-risk-account/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[paygate.to]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 17:40:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[High Risk Payment Gateway]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hide-what-you-are-selling-from-nmi-and-bypass-suspended-high-risk-account/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are you tired of getting banned or restricted by NMI? This is your perfect solution!!! If you are running a high risk business like dropshipping, SMM, SARM or any other form of high risk business you may face a big problem finding a high risk payment processor to accept your business model. Our WooCommerce plugin [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://paygate.to/hide-what-you-are-selling-from-nmi-and-bypass-suspended-high-risk-account/">Hide What You are Selling From NMI and Bypass Suspended High Risk Account</a> appeared first on <a href="https://paygate.to/">PayGate.to</a>.</p>
]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hide What You are Selling From Moolah and Bypass Suspended High Risk Account</title>
		<link>/hide-what-you-are-selling-from-moolah-and-bypass-suspended-high-risk-account/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[paygate.to]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 17:40:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[High Risk Payment Gateway]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hide-what-you-are-selling-from-moolah-and-bypass-suspended-high-risk-account/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are you tired of getting banned or restricted by Moolah? This is your perfect solution!!! If you are running a high risk business like dropshipping, SMM, SARM or any other form of high risk business you may face a big problem finding a high risk payment processor to accept your business model. Our WooCommerce plugin [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://paygate.to/hide-what-you-are-selling-from-moolah-and-bypass-suspended-high-risk-account/">Hide What You are Selling From Moolah and Bypass Suspended High Risk Account</a> appeared first on <a href="https://paygate.to/">PayGate.to</a>.</p>
]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hide What You are Selling From PayU and Bypass Suspended High Risk Account</title>
		<link>/hide-what-you-are-selling-from-payu-and-bypass-suspended-high-risk-account/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[paygate.to]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 17:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[High Risk Payment Gateway]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hide-what-you-are-selling-from-payu-and-bypass-suspended-high-risk-account/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are you tired of getting banned or restricted by PayU? This is your perfect solution!!! If you are running a high risk business like dropshipping, SMM, SARM or any other form of high risk business you may face a big problem finding a high risk payment processor to accept your business model. Our WooCommerce plugin [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://paygate.to/hide-what-you-are-selling-from-payu-and-bypass-suspended-high-risk-account/">Hide What You are Selling From PayU and Bypass Suspended High Risk Account</a> appeared first on <a href="https://paygate.to/">PayGate.to</a>.</p>
]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
